[{"question": " friends. family. we are gathered to celebrate here today the joyous union of ross and emily.  now ross, repeat after me. i ross...", "answer": " i ross...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " take thee, emily...", "answer": " take thee, rachel... emily.  emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  uhh...shall i go on?", "answer": "  he-he said rachel, right? do you think i should go up there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yes, yes, do go on.", "answer": " i think we\u0092d better start again. ross, repeat after me. i, ross\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " i, ross\u009a", "answer": " take thee, em-i-ly\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " as my lawfully wedded wife, in sickness and in health, till death parts us.", "answer": " as my lawfully wedded wife, in sickness and in health, until death parts us. really, i do. emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " may i have the rings?  emily, place this ring on ross\u0092s finger as a symbol of your bond everlasting.  ross, place this ring in emily\u0092s hand as a symbol of the love that encircles you forever.", "answer": " happy too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " ross and emily have made their declarations and it gives me great pleasure to declare them husband and wife.", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " just keep smiling.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, that went well. yeah.", "answer": " it could\u0092ve been worse, he could\u0092ve shot her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  you\u0092ve spoiled everything! it\u0092s like a nightmare! my friends and family are out there! how can i face them?! how can you do this to me?!", "answer": "  hey, no matter what happens with ross and emily, we still get cake right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  that-that-that\u0092s all right, no honey, you take your time sweetie. i\u0092ll be right out here.  she\u0092s just fixing her makeup.", "answer": " i hate you!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " boy, bad time to say the wrong name, huh ross?", "answer": " that\u0092s true, thanks dad.  people should be dancing! huh? hey, this is a party! come on! joey, dance!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yes, waltham interiors.", "answer": "  uh, hello, this is ross geller\u0092s personal physician, dr. philange.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " who?", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092ve discovered that ross forgot to take his brain medicine, uh, now without it, uh, in the brain of ross, uh women\u0092s names are interchangeable, through-through no fault of his own.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh my god, phoebe.", "answer": " no, not phoebe, dr. philange. oh no! you have it too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh wow, i hope you don\u0092t take this the wrong way but, i know we had plans to meet up tonight and, ugh, i\u0092m just kinda worried about what it might do to our friendship.", "answer": " i know. how could we have let this happen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " seven times!", "answer": " ugh! well, y\u0092know, we were away\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " in a foreign, romantic country\u009a", "answer": " i blame london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " so look umm, while we\u0092re st-still in london, i mean, we can keep doing it right?", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t see that we have a choice. but, when we\u0092re back home, we don\u0092t do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " only here.", "answer": " y\u0092know, i saw a wine cellar downstairs\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " i\u0092ll meet you there in two minutes.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " mon, honey, i gotta ask you something.", "answer": "  now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " ross said my name up there, i mean, come on, i just can\u0092t pretend that didn\u0092t happen can i?", "answer": " oh, i-i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " monica, what should i do?", "answer": " just uh, do the right thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " toe the line. thread the needle. think outside the box!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " whoa, wait, listen, i think i\u0092m just gonna talk to ross about what he think it meant.", "answer": " wait. rachel, no, he\u0092s married. married! if you don\u0092t realize that, i can\u0092t help you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " jack, is it all our fault? were we bad parents?", "answer": "  yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh yeah, well who serves steak when there\u0092s no place to sit, i mean how are you supposed to eat this?", "answer": " hey, what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " where were you? we were supposed to meet in the wine cellar?", "answer": " forget it, that\u0092s off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": "  the next tour of the wine cellar will plan in two in-in minutes\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " joey, what are you doing? you promised phoebe you wouldn\u0092t eat meat until she has the babies!", "answer": " well, i figured we\u0092re in another country, so it doesn\u0092t count.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " that\u0092s true.", "answer": " the man\u0092s got a point.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " oh, hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hi. sorry, things aren\u0092t working out so well.", "answer": " oh no! it could be better, but it\u0092s gonna be okay, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh yeah! of course, i mean, she\u0092s gonna get over this, y\u0092know? i mean, so you said my name! y\u0092know you just said it \u0091cause you saw me there, if you\u0092d have seen a circus freak, you would\u0092ve said, \"i take thee circus freak.\" y\u0092know, it didn\u0092t mean anything, it\u0092s just a mistake. it didn\u0092t mean anything. right?", "answer": " no! no! of course it didn\u0092t mean anything! i mean, uh well, i can understand why emily would think it meant something, y\u0092know, because-because it was you\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " right\u009a", "answer": " but it absolutely didn\u0092t.  it didn\u0092t!! it didn\u0092t!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  ross, hey, the band\u0092s ready outside for your first dance with emily, so\u009a", "answer": "  oh! oh-oh, the band\u0092s ready! well, i-i-we gotta do what the band says\u0097i don\u0092t care about the stupid band!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " look, i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " emily is kinda taking a long time, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  y\u0092know when i locked myself in the bathroom at my wedding, it was because i was trying to pop the window out of the frame.", "answer": " oh, right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh my god, rachel! hi!", "answer": " oh, hello rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " ross said my name. okay? my name. ross said my name up there that obviously means that he still loves me!  okay, don\u0092t believe me, i know i\u0092m right\u0097do you guys want to go downstairs and get a drink?", "answer": " yes, we do. but, we have to change first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yes, i want to change. and why-why don\u0092t you go down and get us a table?", "answer": " yeah, we\u0092ll be down in like five minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  fifteen minutes.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " hello? oh, pheebs!  it\u0092s phoebe!", "answer": " oh, yay\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " great\u009a", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hi, so what happened?", "answer": " well, ross said my name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah, i know, but i don\u0092t think that means anything.", "answer": " okay, pheebs, y\u0092know what, let\u0092s look at this objectively all right? ninth grade, right? the obsession starts. all right? the summer after ninth grade he sees me in a two-piece for the first time, his obsession begins to grow. so then\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  hey, listen, why don\u0092t we go change in my room?", "answer": " but my clothes are\u0097ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " wow, you look\u009a", "answer": " no time for that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " hey, dude, let me in. i got a girl out here!", "answer": " well, i\u0092ve got a girl in here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " no you don\u0092t, i just saw you go in there with monica!", "answer": " well, we\u0092re-we\u0092re hanging out in here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " look, which one of us is gonna be having sex in there, me or you?", "answer": " well, i suppose i\u0092d have to say you!! but, what if we\u0092re watching a movie in here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " which we are, and-and we already paid for it. it\u0092s my giant!", "answer": " my giant? i love that movie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " you really think this is okay?", "answer": " well, ross and emily aren\u0092t gonna use", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh, it\u0092s so beautiful. ohh! y\u0092know, i-i don\u0092t know if i feel right about this.", "answer": " oh mon-mon-mon-mon-look, this is the honeymoon suite. the room expects sex. the room would be disappointed if it didn\u0092t get sex. all of the other honeymoon suites would think it was a loser.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  emily?!", "answer": " nope, not under here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t find her?", "answer": " no, i\u0092ve looked everywhere!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " well, you couldn\u0092t have looked everywhere or else you would\u0092ve found her!", "answer": " yeah, i think you should keep looking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " yeah, for about 30 minutes.", "answer": " or 45.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no! for all i know, she\u0092s trying to find me but couldn\u0092t because i kept moving around. no, from now on, i\u0092m staying in one place.  right here.", "answer": " well, it\u0092s getting late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yeah, we\u0092re gonna go.", "answer": " actually, do you guys mind staying here for a while?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " ugh, y\u0092know, umm we gotta get up early and catch that plane for new york.", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s a very large plane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  that\u0092s cool.", "answer": " but, we\u0092ll stay here with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " we have to leave for new york in an hour.", "answer": " i know, i\u0092ve been looking at those doors, they look pretty sound proof, don\u0092t you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " you can forget about emily, she\u0092s not with us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " we\u0092ve come for her things.", "answer": " wait, well wh-wh-wh-where is she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " she\u0092s in hiding. she\u0092s utterly humiliated. she doesn\u0092t want to see you ever again.", "answer": " we\u0092re very sad that it didn\u0092t work out between you and emily, monkey. but, i think you\u0092re absolutely delicious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " excuse me, i\u0092m standing right here!", "answer": " oh yes, there you are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " goodbye geller.", "answer": " now, hold on! hold on!  look, look, your daughter and i are supposed to leave tonight for our honeymoon, now-now you-you tell her that i\u0092m gonna be at that airport and i hope that she\u0092ll be there too! oh yeah, i said rachel\u0092s name, but it didn\u0092t mean anything, okay? she\u0092s-she\u0092s just a friend and that\u0092s all!  that\u0092s all! now just tell emily that i love her and that i can\u0092t imagine spending my life with anyone else. please, promise me that you\u0092ll tell her that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092ll tell her.  come on bugger face!", "answer": "  call me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " y\u0092know, maybe it\u0092s best that we never got to do it again.", "answer": " yeah, it kinda makes that-that one night special.  y\u0092know, technically we still are over international waters.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna go to the bathroom, maybe i\u0092ll see you there in a bit?", "answer": " \u0091kay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " can i ask you something?", "answer": " uhh, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " felicity and i, we\u0092re watching my giant, and i was thinking, \"i\u0092m never gonna be as good an actor as that giant.\" do you think i\u0092m just wasting my life with this acting thing?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i mean, the giant is like five years younger than me, y\u0092know, you think i\u0092ll ever get there?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " thanks man.", "answer": " okay man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " hey, monica, wow you\u0092ve been in the bathroom for like a half-hour.", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " no we didn\u0092t!", "answer": " i know you didn\u0092t, i was talking about monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " phoebe, i did not have sex.", "answer": " this pregnancy is throwing me all off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092m gonna go say hi the chick and the duck.", "answer": " oh, me too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " why would you need to say hi to them, you\u0092ve been feeding them for four days?", "answer": " oh right, maybe i\u0092ll just go home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " well, we certainly are alone.", "answer": " yes! good thing we have that, \u0091not in new york\u0092 rule.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " right. umm, listen since we\u0092re-we-re on that subject, umm, i just wanted to tell you that uh, well, i-i was going through a really hard time in london, what with my brother getting married and that guy thinking i was ross\u0092s mother\u009a", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " well, an-anyway, i just\u0097that night meant a lot to me, i guess i\u0092m just trying to say thanks.", "answer": " oh. y\u0092know, that night meant a lot to me too, and it wasn\u0092t because i was in a bad place or anything, it just meant a lot to me \u0091cause, you\u0092re really hot! is that okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  that\u0092s okay.", "answer": " and i\u0092m cute too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " and you\u0092re cute too.", "answer": " thank you!  all right, i gotta go unpack.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  i\u0092m still on london time, does that count?", "answer": " that counts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " rach! rach!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hi! what are you, what are you doing here?", "answer": " well, i-i-i\u0092ve been on standby for a flight home for hours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " ohh, so no sign of emily huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " not yet.", "answer": " so umm, what time are you supposed to leave?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  this is the last call for flight 1066 to athens. the last call.", "answer": " pretty soon i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " yeah. i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " i just, i don\u0092t understand, i mean, how-how can she do this? y\u0092know, what, am i, am i like a complete idiot for thinking that she\u0092d actually show up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no, you\u0092re not an idiot, ross. you\u0092re a guy very much in love.", "answer": " same difference.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  all ticketed passengers for flight 1066 to athens should now be on board.", "answer": " i get it! well, that\u0092s that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " no, you know what, i think you should go.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " yeah, i do. i think you should go, by yourself, get some distance, clear your head, i think it\u0092d be really good.", "answer": " oh, i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t know\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh, come on ross! i think it would be really good for you!", "answer": " i could, yeah, i can do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " i can\u0092t, i can\u0092t even believe her! no, y\u0092know what, i am, i am gonna go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " good!", "answer": " i know, why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " right!", "answer": " right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " right!", "answer": " y\u0092know\u0097thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " okay, i\u0092ll see you back at home, if i ever get a flight out of here.", "answer": " yeah, well\u009anah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " what? wait, what?", "answer": " why don\u0092t you come, i mean, i-i have two tickets, why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " well-well, i don\u0092t know ross\u0097really?", "answer": " yeah, yeah, it\u0092ll be great! you can, you can lay on the beach and i can cry over my failed marriage. see-see how i make jokes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " no really, i mean, i mean, god, i could use a friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " oh wow, uh okay, uh maybe. umm, yes, i can do that!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " cool!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " all right!", "answer": " come on!  here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh, okay, we\u0092re going. yeah.", "answer": " ah! ah! i forgot my jacket!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh, wait-wait-wait\u009a", "answer": " you tell them to wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}]